Hi guys! Welcome to another video on my channel. I'm still here in Marrakesh on
my holiday trip and I thought I'll use the free time to approach a topic I've
been asked about a lot. How to get my girlfriend into latex. I received this
question on Instagram multiple times so I thought I'll tell you my top five tips.
Point number one. Could she be interested at all in this kind of material? You can
check out if she likes leather leggings at HMM. How does she react when she sees
them? You can check her reaction when she sees a picture of, I don't know, like
someone like Kim Kardashian or someone else wearing latex. Is her reaction like
oh that looks really good or is it like ew what's that that looks really awful
or something. So that could be a first indication about how she feels towards
that topic. And a side note to that point is wearing latex does not mean having a
fetish. I have to stress this out because I've got the impression that all
guys are like oh my god she's wearing latex she has to have a fetish for that
material which is not always the point. I know people who only wear it because it
looks really good and for pictures and makes a nice body shape but they don't
necessarily see this as their fetish. So don't, I don't know, sex it up too much.
don't put her under pressure. You may enjoy it as if it is, so don't think that
she has to feel the same way.
Lovely. Okay, coming to point number two. Find the right approach. I think there
two ways to go with this whole topic. So either you gift her something, so you
make her a present, some latex item and she is surprised by it. Or you kind of
come out of the closet and talk with her about it. So you can explain to her that
you like these kind of materials and then you can try and find something
together with her. So ask her what she would like to wear or how she sees that
stuff and then maybe sit together and go online shopping or go shopping so she
has a say in it. I think it depends on the kind of relationship you have with
your girlfriend which approach you kind of going to choose so think about it and
what would be the best way to do this with your girlfriend I would prefer for
myself I would prefer the second way like going shopping together or having a
say in it because girls are shallow and we want to look good and we want to have
say and what we're going to wear and most of the time women do know better what's going to fit.
Tip number three.
Start with PVC. Don't go into full latex mode from like zero to latex but start with a rather similar
material like PVC or wet look because latex is hard to start with if you don't know what you're
doing. Wearing latex for the first time may be uncomfortable or irritating because you're
sweating a lot so if you're starting with PVC you have the same look on the outside because it's
shiny and women kind of and fashion approach they come together with PVC as
well does it make sense I don't know but PVC is a lot easier to put on than latex
so if she's wearing PVC and she likes it and she feels comfortable you can take
it to the next stage with latex but I wouldn't start with latex right away
Mastering the teeth.
Point number four.
Don't start with a catsuit.
Please don't.
Seriously don't start with a catsuit.
I know that you guys may be really into catsuits because it looks smooth and good but just
don't start with a catsuit when it comes to your girlfriend and latex.
They're really hard to put on, especially for the first time, so they can scare women
off.
So start with something simple, like a dress, a sleeveless dress, a skirt, a top with a
zipper which is going to be easy to put on.
My first latex item was a sleeveless skater dress with a zipper in the front.
So it was really easy and I even wouldn't recommend leggings for the first time because
it needs a lot of practice to really get into them fast.
So don't mess this up because the first time wearing latex, the first experience is an
important one and that one is going to determine the further way of wearing latex.
So if she's not comfortable with it the first time or if you're rushing her, she won't try
it again.
So keep in mind to keep it simple.
Okay, now to the final point.
Buying your first latex piece, or first latex piece for your girlfriend, rather.
So many questions.
Buying an expensive piece at an online shop, at a store where you can visit, or designer piece, whatever.
So, let me tell you about my first experience.
I think it's a good example.
I went to a shop and they had some latex pieces and I asked them, oh can I try a
dress and they were like yeah go ahead go into the cabin change there's some
powder to get into it and they left me alone and I was like okay so what should
I do now and I tried to get into I think it was a dress and I got stuck in the
middle of pulling over my head which was pretty horrible because I don't like
being stuck with my head somewhere and so I left that shop kind of disappointed
because they didn't really take care of customer service and I was kind of what
am I going to do now and then I decided to order a dress online so that's what I
did and it was okay it didn't fit that good because if I would have tried that
dress in the shop I probably wouldn't have bought it because I would have seen
that it didn't fit so yeah it's a bit tricky to buy latex my recommendation is
going into a latex shop and ask the people there for help first for a design
that fits your girlfriend and looks good on her and second for the whole getting into latex know-how
and I prepared a small list because there are a lot of latex designers which do have stores in
big cities for example in Germany you have like chronomatic Peter Domini or Savageware in Berlin
In Hamburg there's Inner Sanctum. In Amsterdam there's a D-mask shop. In London there are a lot of designers.
Pandora Deluxe, Amentium, Libidex, House of Harlot. And in USA there are some as well, which I forgot to write down.
Here we go. I asked Ian, a friend of mine, about US stores and he recommended the Siren
store in LA or NYC, the Baroness and Purple Passion store. And I've even been in a latex
store in Sydney, which was called, what was it named? Max Black. And they had a nice selection
as well. So use Google to find a store in your area. And then there's the issue of
cheap versus expensive latex outfits. Of course you can't do too much damage if
you buy something cheap. There are some Chinese manufacturers. But on the other
hand keep in mind that your girlfriend wants to look good. So maybe take my
advice and buy something from a latex designer. Sorry. Because then you can't be
sure that it will have a good fit and it will probably look better than buying
some cheap non-fitting stuff. Do me a favor keep your hands off from molded
latex except for maybe gloves because it won't fit and it will tear a lot easier.
So to sum everything up, don't start with cat suits. Start slow, start with similar
materials to check out if she likes it. Keep in mind that she wants to look good
and that it is fashion foremost and I'm really sorry to tell you this but there
maybe a chance that she doesn't like latex at all and she'll never wear it.
Sorry. I wish you all the best and a lot of success and if you already did get your girlfriend into
latex, tell me about it. How did she do it? What was her reaction? I seriously don't want to hear
about you as a guy getting into latex because no I don't but I'm really curious about your
girlfriend and her erections and if you have any other tips so have a great day bye